<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>computer science on Moch. Lutfi Tech blog</title>
    <link>https://lumochift.org/tags/computer-science/</link>
    <description>Recent content in computer science on Moch. Lutfi Tech blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 20:02:21 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lumochift.org/tags/computer-science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Computer Science for Humanities</title>
      <link>https://lumochift.org/posts/computer-science-for-humanities/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 20:02:21 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lumochift.org/posts/computer-science-for-humanities/</guid>
      <description>Computer science is no more about computers than astronomy is about telescopes, biology about microscopes, or chemistry about beakers and test tubes. Science is not about tools. It is about how we use them, and what we find out when we do. &amp;mdash; Michael Fellows and Ian Parberry
 Imagine if today without computer technology, maybe we still doing everything in manual way and paper everywhere without gadget, internet connection, smart device, and many things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Am I Lost?</title>
      <link>https://lumochift.org/posts/am-i-lost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 20:02:21 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lumochift.org/posts/am-i-lost/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m proud to be software engineer, programmer, code saint, or whatever you call it 😄. Do you know before I choose Computer Science degree I don&amp;rsquo;t know what the hell Computer Science is. Here the short history about path of my adventure of code. :p
Junior High School Arch In this era I don&amp;rsquo;t know what I&amp;rsquo;m doing and I hate enter Junior High School 1 Malang because I wanted to enter another school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Konsep synchronous dan asynchronous</title>
      <link>https://lumochift.org/posts/async-concept/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 20:02:21 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lumochift.org/posts/async-concept/</guid>
      <description>Dalam postingan pertama ini saya akan sedikit mengulas tentang konsep asynchronous dalam analogi sederhana sehingga bisa memudahkan pembaca dalam memahaminya.
Sebelum itu perlu kita ketahui ada proses synchronous dan asynchronous, apa bedanya? Mari kita simak analogi sederhana berikut.
Untuk penjelasan selanjutnya saya menggunakan istilah sync untuk proses synchronous dan async untuk proses asynchronous.
Pertama-tama akan saya gambarkan dalam bentuk proses yg berurutan:
State awal  Kondisi awal, sedang main DOTA 2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>